module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What is the official name for fear of Friday the 13th?', 
    a: 'Paraskevidekatriaphobia',
    b: 'Spectrophobia',
    c: 'Chorophobia',
    d: 'Arachibutyrophobia',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the movie Friday the 13th\'s original name?', 
    a: 'Saturday the 14th Eve',
    b: 'Herrrrre\'s Jason!',
    c: 'Long Night at Camp Blood',
    d: 'Hockey is for Closers',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was Jason\'s last name in the movie Friday the 13th?', 
    a: 'Statham',
    b: 'Elm',
    c: 'Aldean',
    d: 'Voorhees',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In which movie did the hockey mask become Jason\'s signature look?', 
    a: 'Friday the 13th',
    b: 'Friday the 13th Part II',
    c: 'Friday the 13th Part III',
    d: 'Friday the 13th: The Final Chapter',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the killer in the first Friday the 13th movie?', 
    a: 'Jason Voorhees',
    b: 'Mrs Voorhees',
    c: 'Mr Voorhees',
    d: 'Kevin Bacon',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who created the Friday the 13th story all the movies are based on?', 
    a: 'Victor Miller',
    b: 'Bram Stoker',
    c: 'Wes Craven',
    d: 'Arthur Miller',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many Friday the 13th movies are there?', 
    a: '9',
    b: '10',
    c: '12',
    d: '13',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'When was the first Friday the 13th movie released?', 
    a: '1979',
    b: '1980',
    c: '1982',
    d: '1983',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the camp in Friday the 13th?', 
    a: 'Camp Wo Bee Gone',
    b: 'Camp Gladiator',
    c: 'Camp Crystal Lake',
    d: 'Camp Camp',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was Jason Voorhees weapon of choice?', 
    a: 'Machete',
    b: 'Axe',
    c: 'Knife Fingers',
    d: 'Bombs',
    answer: 'a'
  }
];
